<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Valt - Making Passwords Painless</title>
    <link>https://valt.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Valt - Making Passwords Painless</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://valt.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory Boost</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/memory-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/memory-boost/</guid>
      <description>Valt Passwords challenges you to beat us at our own new game. When you play a round, we display a randomized grid of Valt&amp;rsquo;s curated images. In each row, exactly one of the images is yours. The goal is to accurately select your image as fast as possible from each row. We&amp;rsquo;ll time you. Our intern, John Karabinos, can do it in 15.13 seconds. If you can beat him&amp;mdash;or even come close&amp;mdash;tweet in our direction with the #beatjohn tag!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Gestures Re-innovated</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/contextual-swiping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/contextual-swiping/</guid>
      <description>Contextual Gestures Re-innovated   Starting now, Valt passwords pays attention to your gestures. From your list of accounts on your iOS device, swipe right or left on any one of them to reveal action buttons for copy username, view password, and copy password. If you’re in a hurry, swipe swiftly to the right, and we’ll copy your username straight away. Swipe deliberately to the left, and we’ll copy your password with no questions asked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Coding Theory</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/dual-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/dual-coding/</guid>
      <description>Dual-Coding Theory 100 years ago in a galaxy not so far away, humans discovered that remembering images is easier and faster than remembering text. Despite this fact, billions of online accounts are guarded by strings of letters. To make matters worse, we are constantly advised to choose unique, long, and random character strings that are impossible to remember, one for each of our online accounts. Twenty years ago, researchers showed that more than 27% of people forget their passwords regularly and more than 81% of people forget one or more of their online passwords at least once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valt Holiday Guide to Security</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/holiday-guide-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/holiday-guide-2017/</guid>
      <description>Valt Holiday Guide to Security Holidays: More shopping, more traveling, more exposure of your most sensitive data. Below is our gift to you: how to keep your most critical information safe — so you can spend more time crafting cocktails and less time double-and-triple-checking your online statements for fraud.
While now is a time to celebrate with loved ones, it can also be party season for hackers. Below is our guide to staying secure, while you pop the bubbly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes an Image Memorable?</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/memorable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/memorable/</guid>
      <description>What Makes An Image Memorable?   Many believe memorability is subjective – i.e. the same Facebook pictures will stand out for some but fade away for others. Yet decades of research have proven this false. The ability of an image to stick with someone over time is actually a function of its subject(s) and composition.
Studies show we remember images in proportion to how distinct they are. Strange, counterintuitive pictures will make an impact—e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Valt</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/introducing-valt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/introducing-valt/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Valt   You shop online, you pay your taxes online, you order food online and you talk to your friends online. Let’s face it, the details of your life are stored online.
Now ask yourself, how many online accounts do you have? Is it 20? 30? 50? You might be surprised, but on average people have almost 140 accounts online and by 2020 it will exceed 200. That’s a boatload of usernames and passwords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recognition Memory</title>
      <link>https://valt.io/blog/recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://valt.io/blog/recognition/</guid>
      <description>Recognition Memory   Take a quick look at the six images below.
  Now go back and imagine a single word description for each one. Really, do it. Let me guess, Dancer, Wedding, Sunflower, Owls, Camera, Street. Okay, five out of six ain&amp;rsquo;t bad.
At Valt, we know that humans are extraordinarily good at recognizing images they’ve seen before. In fact, this is one reason Valt is so secure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>